[spooky music]
[幽灵音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[urchins chattering]
[顽童叽叽喳喳]
[ominous music]
[不祥的音乐]
[urchins screaming]
[顽童尖叫]
Biting my begonias, eh?
咬我的海棠吧？
Not on my watch!
[laughs]
不在我的监视之下！
[笑]
Mailman!
邮递员！
Wha...?
世界卫生大会...？
[screams]
[尖叫声]
Oh, a letter.
Uh, thank you!
哦，一封信。
呃，谢谢你！
Nosferatu?
诺斯费拉图？
[lighting cracks]
[灯光裂缝]
Huh?
What?
啊？
什么？
[sighs]
[叹气]
I got his mail by mistake again!
我又错收到他的邮件了！
[grumbles]
[抱怨]
I'll just file that in here.
我就把它归档在这里。
[muffled speech]
[低声说话]
[chuckles]
Huh?
[笑声]
啊？
- [muffled speech]
- SpongeBob?
- [低声说话]
- 海绵宝宝？
[muffled speech]
[低声说话]
What are you doing
in my garbage?
你在做什么
在我的垃圾里？
♪ Spring cleaning ♪
♪ 春季大扫除 ♪
But, Squidward, for shame.
但是，章鱼哥，真是羞耻。
You can't just throw out
the mail of Nosferatu.
你不能直接扔掉
诺斯费拉图的邮件。
[lightning crashes]
- Huh?
[闪电坠毁]
- 啊？
You have to deliver it yourself.
您必须亲自交付。
[gasps]
[喘气]
Otherwise, it'd be
a federal crime!
不然就变成了
联邦犯罪！
And I'll be an accessory!
而我将成为一个附属品！
[hyperventilating]
[换气过度]
All right, already!
I'll take it to him.
好吧，已经！
我会把它带给他。
Hurray!
欢呼！
But you are carrying the mail.
但你正在携带邮件。
Ha!
One little letter?
哈!
一封小信？
- No problemo.
- Hold on.
- 没问题。
- 等等。
There's more.
还有更多。
- Ooh!
- Here's the rest of it.
- 哦！
I have been getting
that creepy guy's mail
我一直在得到
那个令人毛骨悚然的家伙的邮件
by mistake for years!
错误多年！
[gasps]
Squidward, look!
[喘气]
章鱼哥，看！
"Bleeder's Digest."
"Bat Fancy."
《布莱德文摘》。
“蝙蝠幻想。”
"Blood of the Month Club."
“本月俱乐部之血。”
[blood squelches]
[血腥味]
Eh.
呃。
Squidward, do you
know what this means?
章鱼哥，你呢
知道这意味着什么吗？
No.
不。
It means somebody
is going to be very happy
这意味着某人
会很开心
to get all their mail,
somebody named Nosferatu.
获取他们所有的邮件，
一个叫诺斯费拉图的人。
[lightning crashes]
- Ah!
[闪电坠毁]
- 啊！
Huh?
What?
啊？
什么？
What was that?
Stop looking at me.
那是什么？
别再看着我了。
[wolf howls]
[狼嚎]
[whistling melody]
[口哨旋律]
Well, this is the address.
嗯，这就是地址。
[grunts]
- Ooh!
[咕哝]
- 哦！
That castle is so high!
那个城堡好高啊！
[whistling melody]
[口哨旋律]
Please, I beg you,
拜托，我求求你，
do not go to the castle!
The master is a vampire!
不要去城堡！
主人是吸血鬼！
He means to suck your blood!
他的意思是要吸你的血！
[sobbing]
[抽泣]
- What are you talking about?
- Nosferatu!
- 你在说什么？
- 诺斯费拉图！
[lightning crashes]
[闪电坠毁]
- Mm-hmm.
- [laughs]
- 嗯嗯。
- [笑]
Right.
I'm sorry.
正确的。
对不起。
I don't have any spare change.
我没有零钱。
Don't go to the castle!
别去城堡！
Don't go...
[skeletal seahorse neighs]
别走...
[骷髅海马嘶鸣]
[snarls]
[咆哮]
- Ow!
- Ah!
- 噢！
- 啊！
Well, a coach to the castle.
How elegant.
嗯，有去城堡的长途汽车。
多么优雅啊。
Step lively, SpongeBob.
- [grunting]
行动起来吧，海绵宝宝。
- [咕哝]
[humming melody]
- [gasps]
[哼唱的旋律]
- [喘气]
- The castle!
- Aw.
- 城堡！
- 噢。
Looks like someone
could use a Krabby Patty.
看起来像某人
可以用蟹肉饼。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[chuckles]
[笑声]
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[both grunting]
[两人都咕哝着]
♪ ♪
♪♪
Whoo!
呼！
♪ ♪
♪♪
- Whoa!
- Oh, whoa!
- 哇！
- 哦，哇！
♪ ♪
♪♪
We're taking
the bus on the way home!
我们正在采取
回家路上的公交车！
- [grunts]
- Huh?
- [咕哝]
- 啊？
Hmm.
唔。
[eerie organ music]
[怪异的管风琴音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[wolf howls]
[狼嚎]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[both grunt]
[两人咕哝]
[grumbling]
[抱怨]
[knocks]
[敲门声]
Hello, Nosferatu?
你好，诺斯费拉图？
[lightning crashes]
Hmm.
[闪电坠毁]
嗯。
Well, looks like nobody's home.
嗯，看来没人在家。
Of course.
当然。
Hello?
你好？
We're just here
to drop off your mail.
我们就在这里
投递您的邮件。
Whoa!
哇！
[lightning crashes]
- [screams]
[闪电坠毁]
- [尖叫]
What's happening?
发生什么事了？
[snickering]
[窃笑]
Aw!
It's just Nosferatu!
噢！
这只是诺斯费拉图！
[lightning crashes]
- Whew!
[闪电坠毁]
- 哇！
[eerie music]
[怪异音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
- [hisses]
- [screams]
- [嘶嘶声]
- [尖叫]
[plucky music]
[勇敢的音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
The master bids you welcome,
主人恭候您的光临，
and he thanks you
for dropping off his mail.
他谢谢你
投递他的邮件。
Oh.
哦。
Ooh.
[belches]
[打嗝]
[giggles]
- [laughs]
[咯咯笑]
- [笑]
[laughs]
[笑]
- [laughs]
- [笑]
[laughter]
[笑声]
Hmm?
[groans]
唔？
[呻吟]
[laughter]
[笑声]
Knock it off!
- I am sorry, Master.
关掉它！
- 对不起，师父。
It won't happen again.
这样的事不会再发生了。
Ew.
We'll let ourselves out.
呃。
我们会放飞自我。
Aw, I don't want to leave.
唉，我不想离开。
Boo!
嘘！
[lightning crashes]
- Ah!
[闪电坠毁]
- 啊！
Oh, you can't leave
due to inclement weather.
哦，你不能离开
由于恶劣天气。
We can't leave yet.
Yay!
我们还不能离开。
耶！
[eerie music]
[怪异音乐]
Gulp.
咕噜咕噜。
The Master has invited you
to stay for the night,
大师邀请你了
留下来过夜，
but first, he would like
to have you both for dinner.
但首先他想
请你们俩共进晚餐。
[laughs]
[笑]
Well, uh,
under the circumstances,
嗯，呃，
在这种情况下，
I wouldn't mind some
fine Transylvanian cuisine
我不介意一些
精致的特兰西瓦尼亚美食
for a change.
- Change?
为了改变。
- 改变？
I can make change.
[laughs]
我可以做出改变。
[笑]
Get away from me.
离我远点。
[snorting and chuckling]
Come, come.
[哼哼和咯咯笑]
来吧，来吧。
- Oh, oh.
- [laughs]
- 哦，哦。
- [笑]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[laughs]
[笑]
[gentle violin music]
[轻柔的小提琴音乐]
Wow!
What a spread.
哇！
多么广泛啊。
I don't know what to try first.
我不知道先尝试什么。
Oh, I can help you decide.
[laughs]
哦，我可以帮你决定。
[笑]
We have roasted werewolf teeth,
我们有烤狼人的牙齿，
pickled demon beards,
fried mummy fingers,
腌制的恶魔胡须，
炸妈妈手指，
and brains tartare.
- [retches]
和鞑靼的大脑。
- [干呕]
Ooh, don't mind if I do... oh.
[laughs]
哦，别介意我这样做……哦。
[笑]
Or maybe you would like
something sinfully succulent.
或者也许你会想要
罪恶多汁的东西。
Ooh, a Carpathian cheese ball.
哦，喀尔巴阡奶酪球。
Uh, eh.
- Whoopsie!
呃，呃。
- 哎哟！
That's my dinner.
Come to daddy!
这就是我的晚餐。
来爸爸身边吧！
- Ooh.
- [groans]
- 哦。
- [呻吟]
Oh, you've got to try
these mummy fingers, Squidward.
哦，你必须尝试一下
这些木乃伊手指，章鱼哥。
So delicious.
真好吃。
Nosferatu, you simply
must give me the recipe.
诺斯费拉图，你只是
必须给我食谱。
Hm.
嗯。
[woman screams]
[女人尖叫]
Well, maybe if I put
some ketchup on it.
好吧，也许如果我把
上面放一些番茄酱。
[munching]
Ketchup?
[咀嚼]
番茄酱？
Good thing I came prepared.
还好我有备而来。
Ketching up!
番茄酱！
[energetic music]
[充满活力的音乐]
Hmm.
Ah.
唔。
啊。
[laughs]
Whoa!
[笑]
哇！
[sighs]
[叹气]
[growls]
[咆哮]
[slurps]
[啜饮]
[gags]
- Nosferatu, ketchup?
[笑点]
- 诺斯费拉图，番茄酱？
Whoa!
- Mm-hm.
哇！
- 嗯嗯。
[sighs]
- [laughs]
[叹气]
- [笑]
[hisses]
[嘶嘶声]
The Master says, "Sleep tight
师父说：“睡个好觉吧
and don't let
the vampire bats bite."
并且不要让
吸血蝙蝠会咬人。”
[laughs]
[笑]
[laughter]
[笑声]
[hisses]
[嘶嘶声]
The Master bids you good night.
大师向您道晚安。
[laughs softly]
[轻笑]
Good night, Nosferatu!
晚安，诺斯费拉图！
[eerie organ music]
[怪异的管风琴音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
This place gives me the creeps.
这个地方让我毛骨悚然。
But so what?
It's only one night.
但那又怎样呢？
这只是一晚。
Right, SpongeB...
对了，海绵宝宝……
[snoring]
[打鼾]
- Huh?
- Whoops!
- 啊？
- 哎呀！
Forgot to brush my teeth.
忘记刷牙了。
[tense music]
[紧张的音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[snoring]
Whoops!
[打鼾]
哎呀！
Forgot to floss.
- Huh?
忘记用牙线。
- 啊？
[snoring]
Ooh!
[打鼾]
哦！
Forgot to wash my head.
- Huh?
忘记洗头了。
- 啊？
Whoops!
Forgot to polish my eyes.
哎呀！
忘记擦亮眼睛了。
Huh?
啊？
Will you go
night night time already?
你会去吗
已经晚上了吗？
Nosferatu?
诺斯费拉图？
Why are you sticking out
of the wall like that?
你为什么坚持
是这样的墙吗？
[hisses]
[嘶嘶声]
[screams]
[尖叫声]
I can't believe Nosferatu
tried to bite me!
我不敢相信诺斯费拉图
试图咬我！
He's a real life v-v-vampire!
他是现实生活中的吸血鬼！
He's gonna suck our blood!
[sobs]
他会吸干我们的血！
[抽泣]
There's got to be
a way out of this castle!
一定有
离开这座城堡的出路！
I can show you a way out!
我可以给你指一条出路！
[laughs]
[笑]
Slappy sleepy.
昏昏欲睡。
Let's try these doors!
让我们试试这些门吧！
[snarls]
[咆哮]
[both scream]
[两人尖叫]
[laughter]
[笑声]
[both scream]
[两人尖叫]
[both hyperventilating]
[双方都过度换气]
[together]
Gorilla monster!
[一起]
大猩猩怪物！
[both scream]
[两人尖叫]
Quick, down the laundry chute!
快，从洗衣槽下去！
[screams]
[尖叫声]
[loud thud]
[巨响]
- Whoa!
- [screaming]
- 哇！
- [尖叫]
[both scream]
[两人尖叫]
It's a vampire's coffin!
[whimpers]
这是吸血鬼的棺材！
[呜咽]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
Nosferatu two-step!
诺斯费拉图两步走！
♪ ♪
♪♪
Yay!
Ow.
耶！
噢。
Snap out of it, SpongeBob!
海绵宝宝，振作起来！
What if he bites our necks...
[gasps]
如果他咬住我们的脖子怎么办？
[喘气]
Or my nose?
- Oh!
还是我的鼻子？
- 哦！
I know what to do.
我知道该怎么做。
In those vampire movies,
they always make wooden stakes.
那些吸血鬼电影里，
他们总是做木桩。
[gasps]
That's a great idea!
[喘气]
这是个好主意！
Here!
这里！
[cow moos]
[牛哞哞]
Will these even work
without steak sauce?
这些还能用吗
没有牛排酱？
[both scream]
[两人尖叫]
You shouldn't disturb
the master's laundry tomb.
你不应该打扰
主人的洗衣墓。
He would be very cranky
if he found you here,
他会很暴躁
如果他在这里找到你
and you never know
where he might be.
你永远不知道
他可能在哪里。
He's right behind us, isn't he?
他就在我们后面，不是吗？
Hmm?
Nope.
唔？
没有。
Nobody there.
We're fine.
那里没有人。
我们很好。
[both scream]
[两人尖叫]
Please don't eat us!
请不要吃我们！
Oh, the master is not hungry.
哦，主人不饿。
He just had a big lunch.
他刚刚吃了一顿丰盛的午餐。
He wanted to return your mail.
他想退回你的邮件。
Oh.
Well, how thoughtful of you.
哦。
嗯，你想得真周到。
Uh, thanks.
- Ooh!
呃，谢谢。
- 哦！
Open it, Squidward!
打开它，章鱼哥！
What'd you get?
- Let's see.
你得到了什么？
- 让我们来看看。
Oh, yes!
哦是的！
It's my Garlic
of the Month Club!
这是我的大蒜
月俱乐部！
Wait.
Uh-oh.
等待。
呃哦。
[gagging]
[作呕]
[chuckles]
[笑声]
The master
is just joshing with you.
大师
只是跟你开玩笑。
He loves garlic.
他喜欢大蒜。
[laughter]
- Um.
[笑声]
- 嗯。
Oh!
[laughter]
哦！
[笑声]
- Huh?
- Mm-mm-mm.
- 啊？
- 毫米-毫米-毫米。
Well, if you're not flicking
the lights on and off,
好吧，如果你不轻弹的话
灯的打开和关闭，
then who is?
那么是谁呢？
[eerie organ music]
[怪异的管风琴音乐]
[together]
Phantom of the Opera!
[一起]
歌剧魅影！
[laughs]
[笑]
[laughter]
[笑声]